{
    "subject": "resource/Suman_(actor)",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Karnataka",
    "human_readable": "Suman was born in Karnataka.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9230762720108032,
            "question": "Is Suman from Karnataka?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9080635905265808,
            "question": "Did Suman originate from Karnataka?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8028350472450256,
            "question": "In which state was Suman born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7669428586959839,
            "question": "Where was Suman born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6650238633155823,
            "question": "What is the name of the state where Suman was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5433840155601501,
            "question": "What is the location of Suman's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45833778381347656,
            "question": "Suman's place of birth is...?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42183807492256165,
            "question": "Can you tell me Suman's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34856468439102173,
            "question": "To which state does Suman belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28061845898628235,
            "question": "Where was Suman brought into the world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Suman was born in Karnataka.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8033_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which state does Suman belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8033_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me Suman's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8033_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Suman's place of birth is...?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8033_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8033_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8033_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8033_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8033_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8033_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8033_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8033_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8033_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8033_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8033_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there are multiple individuals named Suman mentioned in the documents, and only one of them (Suman Ranganath) was born in Bangalore, Karnataka. The other Sumans mentioned were not explicitly stated to have been born in Karnataka."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the information provided in `17.txt` which states, \"Suman...was born in Karnataka, and made a name in Telugu.\" This supports the statement that Suman was born in Karnataka."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Suman mentioned at the pre-release event of Seva Daas that he was born in Karnataka, but his birthplace as stated in another context information is actually Regunta village of Karimnagar district of Telangana (erstwhile Andhra Pradesh).",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}